Fri Sep 18 2015 13:19:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 13:19:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 13:19:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5010Fri Sep 18 2015 13:19:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 13:19:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 13:19:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5010Fri Sep 18 2015 13:20:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 13:20:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 13:20:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5010Fri Sep 18 2015 13:22:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 13:22:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 13:22:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5010Fri Sep 18 2015 14:10:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 14:10:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 14:10:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5010Fri Sep 18 2015 15:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 15:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:22:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 15:22:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 15:32:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 15:32:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Fri Sep 18 2015 15:32:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Fri Sep 18 2015 15:32:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesFri Sep 18 2015 23:26:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Fri Sep 18 2015 23:26:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:19:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:19:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 00:19:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 00:19:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:19:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 00:20:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request!Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 14:02:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660533167-5572Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660534167-5570Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660539167-5573Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660540167-5571Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660545166-5574Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660546167-5572Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660551168-5575Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660552167-5573Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660557167-5576Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660558167-5574Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660563167-5577Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660564167-5575Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660569168-5578Sat Sep 19 2015 14:02:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660570167-5576Sat Sep 19 2015 14:03:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660591683-0Sat Sep 19 2015 14:03:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660592769-1Sat Sep 19 2015 14:03:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660594780-2Sat Sep 19 2015 14:03:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660597791-3Sat Sep 19 2015 14:03:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442660601803-4Sat Sep 19 2015 14:34:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 14:34:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 14:34:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 14:58:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663939554-0Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663940646-1Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663942667-2Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663945688-3Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663949727-4Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663954738-5Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663959751-6Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663964771-7Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663970167-8Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663976167-9Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663982167-10Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663988167-11Sat Sep 19 2015 14:59:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442663994167-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664000167-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664006168-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664012167-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664018167-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664024167-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664030167-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664036167-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664042167-20Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664048167-21Sat Sep 19 2015 15:00:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664054167-22Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664060167-23Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664066167-24Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664072167-25Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664078167-26Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664084167-27Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664090168-28Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664096167-29Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664102167-30Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664108167-31Sat Sep 19 2015 15:01:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664114167-32Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664120167-33Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664126167-34Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664132167-35Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664138167-36Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664144167-37Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664150167-38Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664156167-39Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664162167-40Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664168167-41Sat Sep 19 2015 15:02:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664174168-42Sat Sep 19 2015 15:03:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664180167-43Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664249174-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664250269-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664252283-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664255300-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664259315-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664264327-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664269340-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664274357-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664279370-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664284383-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664289394-10Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664294408-11Sat Sep 19 2015 15:04:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664299421-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664304441-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664309459-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664314472-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664319482-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664324494-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664329508-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664334528-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664339545-20Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664344567-21Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664349583-22Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664353693-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664354784-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664356798-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:05:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664359812-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664364347-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664365439-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664367453-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664370471-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664374776-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664375865-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664377877-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664380892-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664384911-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664389925-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664392089-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664393176-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664395192-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664398204-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664402215-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664407229-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664412248-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:06:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664417262-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664563270-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664564361-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664566375-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664569389-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664573418-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664578432-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664583445-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664588458-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664593473-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:09:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664598484-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664603497-10Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664608508-11Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664613521-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664619167-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664625167-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664631167-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664637167-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664643167-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664649168-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:10:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664655167-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664661167-20Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664667167-21Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664673168-22Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664674930-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664676040-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664678070-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664681083-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664685097-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664690109-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664695122-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664700137-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664705151-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664710169-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664714452-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664715550-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:11:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664717565-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664720587-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664724602-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664729615-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664734630-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664739652-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664744666-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664749679-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664754703-10Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664759718-11Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664764730-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664770167-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:12:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664776167-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664782167-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664788167-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664794167-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664800167-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664806167-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664812167-20Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664818167-21Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664824167-22Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664830167-23Sat Sep 19 2015 15:13:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664836167-24Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664842167-25Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664848167-26Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664854167-27Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664860167-28Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664866167-29Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664872167-30Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664878167-31Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664884167-32Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664890167-33Sat Sep 19 2015 15:14:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664896167-34Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664902167-35Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664908167-36Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664914167-37Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664920167-38Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664926167-39Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664932167-40Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664938167-41Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664944167-42Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664950167-43Sat Sep 19 2015 15:15:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664956167-44Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664962167-45Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664968167-46Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664973140-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664974249-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664976266-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664979285-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664983305-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664989167-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442664995167-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665001167-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665007167-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665013167-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:16:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665019167-10Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665025167-11Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665031167-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665037167-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665043167-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665049167-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665055167-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665061167-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665067167-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665073166-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665076058-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665077160-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:17:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665079179-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665082191-3Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665086217-4Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665091231-5Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665096243-6Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665101259-7Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665106274-8Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665111287-9Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665116304-10Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665121319-11Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665126332-12Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665131347-13Sat Sep 19 2015 15:18:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665136359-14Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665141374-15Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665146387-16Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665151405-17Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665156419-18Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665161432-19Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665166446-20Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665171461-21Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665176480-22Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665181497-23Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665186512-24Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665191528-25Sat Sep 19 2015 15:19:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665196544-26Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665201559-27Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665206575-28Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665211589-29Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665216601-30Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665221619-31Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665226634-32Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665231651-33Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665236668-34Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665238772-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665239890-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665241905-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665244432-0Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665245539-1Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665247556-2Sat Sep 19 2015 15:20:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442665250573-3Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:13:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686389167-216Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686395167-217Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686401167-218Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686407167-219Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686413167-220Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686419167-221Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686425167-222Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686431167-223Sat Sep 19 2015 21:13:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686437167-224Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686443167-225Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686449167-226Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686455167-227Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686461167-228Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686467167-229Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686473167-230Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686479167-231Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686485167-232Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686491167-233Sat Sep 19 2015 21:14:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686497167-234Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686503167-235Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686509167-236Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686515167-237Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686521167-238Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686527167-239Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686533167-240Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686539167-241Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686545167-242Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686551167-243Sat Sep 19 2015 21:15:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686557167-244Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686563167-245Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686569167-246Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686575167-247Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686581167-248Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686587167-249Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686593167-250Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686599167-251Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686605167-252Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686611168-253Sat Sep 19 2015 21:16:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686617167-254Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686623167-255Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686629167-256Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686635167-257Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686641167-258Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686647167-259Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686653167-260Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686659167-261Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686665167-262Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686671167-263Sat Sep 19 2015 21:17:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686677167-264Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686683167-265Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686689167-266Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686695167-267Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686701167-268Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686707167-269Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686713166-270Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686719167-271Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686725167-272Sat Sep 19 2015 21:18:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686731167-273Sat Sep 19 2015 21:19:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:19:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:19:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:19:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686782131-282Sat Sep 19 2015 21:19:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686787167-283Sat Sep 19 2015 21:19:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//socket.io/?EIO=3&transport=polling&t=1442686792192-284Sat Sep 19 2015 21:28:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:28:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:28:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 21:32:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 21:32:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:34:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:35:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 21:35:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 21:35:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 21:35:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 21:42:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:42:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:42:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:43:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 21:43:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"6","logins":["Raja",""]}Sat Sep 19 2015 21:43:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) Cannot find tournament with ID=6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"6","logins":["Raja",""]}Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:6 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:6 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <6> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <6> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 21:44:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 21:44:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:57:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 21:57:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 21:58:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 21:58:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:03:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:03:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:05:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 22:05:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:06:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:06:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:06:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:07:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 22:07:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:08:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:08:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:09:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 22:09:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:10:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 22:10:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:11:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:11:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 22:11:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:12:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 22:12:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 7 in tournament 7 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sat Sep 19 2015 22:13:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"7","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:7 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) 7Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:31:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:7/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 7 in tournament 7 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:32:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSat Sep 19 2015 23:32:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <7> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"6","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:6 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:6 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <6> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <6> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) 6Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:51 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:35:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:35:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:6/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 6 in tournament 6 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:36:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"5","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:5 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:5 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <5> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <5> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:37:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:37:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:38:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:5/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 5 in tournament 5 ends. Raja wins!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:38:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"4","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:4 playerID:0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:4 playerID:1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <4> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:40:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSat Sep 19 2015 23:40:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <4> got new playerSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:4/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 4 in tournament 4 ends. Raja wins!!Sat Sep 19 2015 23:41:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"3","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:39 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 3 in tournament 3 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:00:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"2","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 2 in tournament 2 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:04:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"1","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:1 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:1 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <1> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <1> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:28 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 1 in tournament 1 ends. Raja wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:11:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"1","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:1 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:1 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <1> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:33 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:34 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <1> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:37 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:12:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:12:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:13:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:13:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:1/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Raja":1,"Alvaro_Fernandez":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 1 in tournament 1 ends. Raja wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:13:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:15:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:15:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"2","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:03 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 2 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Raja":1,"Alvaro_Fernandez":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 2 in tournament 2 ends. Raja wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:16:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:20:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:20:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"2","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:21:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:21:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:22:54 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"2","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:08 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:14 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 2 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:26 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:36 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Alvaro_Fernandez":0,"Raja":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 2 in tournament 2 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:23:40 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"2","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:2 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <2> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:33:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 2 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:06 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:16 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:2/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 4 , while correct is :4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:21 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Raja":6,"Alvaro_Fernandez":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSun Sep 20 2015 00:34:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 2 in tournament 2 ends. Raja wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:34:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"3","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:41 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:42 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:43 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:52 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:53 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:36:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:04 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:11 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :4Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:18 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Alvaro_Fernandez":3,"Raja":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: Alvaro_FernandezSun Sep 20 2015 00:37:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 3 in tournament 3 ends. Alvaro_Fernandez wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 00:37:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:29 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:30 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:31 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"3","logins":["Raja","Alvaro_Fernandez"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 13:27:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:58 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:27:59 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:07 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:09 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 2 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:13 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:17 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:22 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:24 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:27 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:32 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 4 , while correct is :4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:28:35 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:29:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) GMM Server starts!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:29:56 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to StartGameServerSun Sep 20 2015 13:29:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Example app listening at http://:::5009Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:01 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//ServeGamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game Server serves gamesSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!!!   var gameID = data[tournamentID];Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) GameServer: Request//StartGameSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) start game: {"sender":"TournamentServer","tournamentID":"3","logins":["Alvaro_Fernandez","Raja"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) custom init works! gameID:3 playerID:1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) PlayersSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) [object Object]Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:44 GMT+0300 (MSK) AnsweredSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new playerSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:45 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:46 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:47 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:48 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:49 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/startGame/{"ticks":0}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Trying to stop timerSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:50 GMT+0300 (MSK) Stopped timerSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:55 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 1 , while correct is :1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 0Sun Sep 20 2015 13:30:57 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый цвет","answers":["Красный","Зелёный","Золотой","Синий"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:00 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 2 , while correct is :2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 1Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:02 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин САМЫЙ любимый футболист","answers":["Модрич","Зидан","Рамос","Хамес"],"correct":2}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 2Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"],"correct":1}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:05 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин возраст","answers":["20","21","19","13"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:10 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:12 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагина любимая еда","answers":["хачапури","шашлык","отбивная","хинкали"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:15 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 3 , while correct is :3Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:19 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый футбольный клуб","answers":["Барселона","МЮ","Реал Мадрид","Челси"],"correct":3}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) Rewrite getQuestions function!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:20 GMT+0300 (MSK) SendToRoom:3/update/{"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"]}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX Action AnswerIsCorrect!!! IF PLAYER WILL PRESS ALL ANSWERS FASTLY, HE WILL INCREASE HIS POINTSSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) Player answer = 4 , while correct is :4Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) questIndex = 5Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:23 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"question":"Гагин любимый язык программирования","answers":["js","Java","C++","C#"],"correct":4}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) AsyncUpdate. be aware of  Questions.length!!! it must be games[gameID].QuestionsSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) {"Alvaro_Fernandez":0,"Raja":5}Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Winner is: RajaSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) Game 3 in tournament 3 ends. Raja wins!!Sun Sep 20 2015 13:31:25 GMT+0300 (MSK) FIX IT!!! GAMEID=tournamentIDSun Sep 20 2015 13:31:38 GMT+0300 (MSK) Room <3> got new player